Guide to the Sarah G. Jacobson Papers MSS.157
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Miscellaneous Media Originals
  - Subseries C: Video Recordings, Independent Media
    Subseries C contains donated elements, video cassettes (VHS) of works by independent filmmakers that Jacobson knew. Some items contain annotated notes and correspondence from the artist. See Series IV and Series VI for related materials. Arranged alphabetically by director or title. Access copies may not be available for consulation, please ask a Fales archivist.
    - Directed by Amini, Cyprus Chicken Village, undated; ID: 157.0239 (Box 33, Media ID: 157.0239)
      Original format: Video Recording (VHS), Donated Element
      Duration: 53 minutes
    - Avenue Amy Episodes 1-6, undated; ID: 157.0240 (Box 33, Media ID: 157.0240)
      Duration: unknown
    - Tony Arena: Act Up Video Projects, undated; ID: 157.0241 (Box 33, Media ID: 157.0241)
    - Fred Armisen's Guide to Music and South by Southwest '98, 1998; ID: 157.0242 (Box 33, Media ID: 157.0242)
      Duration: 21 minutes
    - Big Miss Moviola Presents, Joanie 4 Jackie 4Ever, 1998; ID: 157.0243 (Box 33, Media ID: 157.0243)
      Duration: 2 hours 15 minutes
    - BNS Productions, Billy Nayer, The Man on the Moon and The Ketchup and Mustard Man, 1992-1998; ID: 157.0262 (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0262)
      Duration: 57 minutes
    - A Phil Bottie Home Movie, Middletown, 1996 (Box 33, Media ID: 157.0244)
    - Directed by Carol Cassidy and Ruth Leitman, Wildwood, New Jersey, undated (Box 33, Media ID: 157.0245)
      TRT: 01:00:00
    - Directed by Alan Chebot, Wild Wild Web, Episode 121, 1998 (Box 33, Media ID: 157.0246)
    - Directed by Dulcie Clarkson, How the Miracle of Masturbation Saved me from Becoming a Teenaged Space Alien, undated (Box 33, Media ID: 157.0247)
      TRT: 00:22:00
    - Crosley Fiver, 1993 (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0278)
      TRT: 00:20:00
    - Directed by Tamra Davis Boss Hog -- I Dig You and Amps -- Pacer, undated (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0248)
    - Directed by Michael W. Dean, DIY or Die: How to Survive As an Independent Artist, undated (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0249)
      TRT: 00:58:00
    - Directed by Andrew Dickson, Good Grief, 1998 (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0250)
      TRT: 01:18:00
    - Katrina Del Mar Presents, Gang Girls 2000, 1999 (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0251)
      TRT: 00:27:00
    - Empty Records/ Rodeo Filmco, Scared of Chaka -- Automatic, undated (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0252)
    - Directed by Ron Faris, Running With Scissors, undated (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0253)
      TRT: 00:12:00
    - Directed by Mary Gillen, Blue Star, 1999 (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0254)
      TRT: 00:48:00
    - Directed by Frank Grow, Red and Rosy, undated (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0255)
    - Go Cart Records, The Luna Chicks Say What You Mean, undated (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0256)
      TRT: 00:02:30
    - Directed by Julian P Hobbs, Collectors, undated (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0257)
      Format: Video Recording (VHS), Donated Element that includes paper element
      TRT: O1:27:00
    - Impossible Funky Productions, Who Do You Think You're Fooling?, undated (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0276)
      TRT: 00:11:00
    - Directed by Sarah Kernochan, Thoth, undated (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0258)
      TRT: 00:42:00
    - Directed by George Kuchar, Dingleberry Jingles and Society Slut, undated (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0259)
    - KXAN 10PM News, RE: Jim Swift Movie Premiere, 03/16/98, 1998 (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0269)
      TRT: 00:02:45
    - Directed by Sara McCool, Big Girls, 2000 (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0260)
      TRT: 00:25:00
    - Directed by Matt McCormick, The Vyrotonin Decision (RT: 7:00)and Sincerely, Joe P. Bear (RT: 4:00), undated (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0261)
    - Pros and Cons,The Calling, and The Expert Larissa, undated (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0263)
    - Red Aunts, Roller Derby Queen, 1995 (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0264)
      TRT: 00:02:07
    - Red Aunts, Salt Box, undated (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0265)
    - Directed by Scott Saunders, The Technical Writer, 2003 (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0266)
      TRT: 01:35:00
    - Directed by Scott Saunders,Welcome to WillieWorld, undated (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0267)
      TRT: 00:13:37
    - Directed by Greta Snider, Portland, undated (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0280)
    - Directed by Tara Spartz, I Hate Baby-Sitting!, undated (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0279)
      TRT: 01:10:00
    - Steel Tree Films, Rat Bastard, 2003 (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0268)
    - No Tommy Pictures, Angels?, undated (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0270)
    - Texas Student Televsion Sneak Peek, Special Edition #9, Cue Time: 01:30, Run Time: 27:00 (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0271)
      TRT: 00:28:30
    - Directed by Corin Tucker, A Riot Grrl Tells Her Own Story, To Sarah (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0282)
      TRT: 00:07:00
    - Urgh! A Music War, NTSC, undated (Box 34, Media ID: 157.0272)
    - Directed by Todd Verow Shucking the Curve, 1999 (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0273)
      TRT: 01:29:00
    - Directed by Jeff Vilencia Smush, 1993 (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0274)
      TRT: 00:08:30
    - Directed by Whitney Ward, Self Totalled Amphetamine Reptile Records Cosmic Psychos, Whip Me, undated (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0275)
      TRT: 00:04:23
    - Young Americans: Katrina Flener, Courtney Little, Chris Talbott and Ari Vena The Fourth, 1998 (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0277)
      TRT: 00:29:00
  - Subseries D: Video Recording (VHS), Other
    Subseries D contains miscellaneous video recordings of commercially produced feature-length films.
    - ABC TV, 9/25/95, 1995 (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0281)
    - "90210 -- Prom", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0283)
    - "CHIPs and More! featuring PAIN", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0284)
    - "Cocksucker Blues", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0285)
    - "Courtney vs Madonna on MTV", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0286)
    - "Courtney, Roseanne, Courtney on Barbara Walters, Roseanne on Letterman", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0287)
    - "The Dark Ages -- Twin/Tone Collector; Agit Pop -- Stop, Drop and Rolle; Magnolias -- Walk a Circle; Mekons -- Ghosts of American Astronauts; Soul Asylum -- P-9; Suicide Cammandos -- Burn it Down; Sat Nite Live -- Replacements", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0288)
    - Syd Field's Screenwriting Workshop: Video Learning Series Part 1, 1999 (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0289)
      TRT: 00:57:00
    - Syd Field's Screenwriting Workshop: Video Learning Series Part 2, 1999 (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0290)
    - Directed by Larry Gross, 3:15 The Moment of Truth, 1986 (Box 15, Media ID: 157.0314)
      TRT: 01:26:00
    - Chris Harvey, On Any Third Sunday, 1993 (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0291)
    - "Hole on SNL; X-Files and SNL", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0292)
    - Directed by Jeffery F. Jackson Death and Taxes, 1993 (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0293)
      TRT: 01:30:00
    - Directed by Jeff Krulik On The Bus, 1997 (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0294)
      TRT: 00:45:00
    - "Law and Order", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 157.0295)
    - Directed by Dave Markey, 1991: The Year That Punk Broke, 1999 (Box 15, Media ID: 157.0298)
    - Manson, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 157.0296)
    - Directed by, Alan Moyle, Pump Up The Volume, 1990 (Box 15, Media ID: 157.0297)
      TRT: 01:45:00
    - "Punk Rock Quincy", undated (Box 15, Media ID: 157.0299)
    - "Popcorn Tryouts", undated (Box 15, Media ID: 157.0300)
    - Postal Worker, Promotional Trailer, 1995 (Box 15, Media ID: 157.0301)
      TRT: 00:06:00
    - Directed by Jacques Rivette, Celine and June Go Boating, 1997 (Box 15, Media ID: 157.0302)
      TRT: 03:33:00
    - "Roseanne Final Episode", 1999 (Box 15, Media ID: 157.0303)
    - "Sex Pistols on Bill Grundy; Rock N' Roll High School w/ Audio Commentary", undated (Box 15, Media ID: 157.0304)
    - "Skills To Pay The Bills, Beastie Boys; Goo, Sonic Youth", undated (Box 15, Media ID: 157.0305)
    - "Sonic Youth, 100%", undated (Box 15, Media ID: 157.0306)
    - Directed by Penelope Spheeris The Boys Next Door, 1990 (Box 15, Media ID: 157.0310)
    - "Starstruck", undated (Box 15, Media ID: 157.0307)
    - "Suburban Sluts From Hell", undated (Box 15, Media ID: 157.0308)
    - "Twitch Party at the Whiskey; Melvins Videos", undated (Box 15, Media ID: 157.0309)
    - Directed by John Waters, Pink Flamingos, 25th Anniversary Edition, 1997 (Box 15, Media ID: 157.0311)
      TRT: 01:48:00
    - White Trash Girl Says... "Suck My Dick!", undated (Box 15, Media ID: 157.0312)
    - "The Wizard of Oz", undated (Box 15, Media ID: 157.0313)
  - Subseries E: Film, Undated; 1 film reels (Box 47, Film 157.501)
- Series VI: Other Authors
  Series VI contains materials produced by other authors used by Jacobson for research, interest-sake or otherwise. Arranged alphabetically either by last name or project title according to Jacobson's original order. Quotation marks are used to indicate Jacobson's original folder title.
  - Other Authors
    - "Other People's Film," Karen Alder, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 276)
    - "Gillian Armstrong", 1999 (Box 5, Folder 277)
    - "Baise-Moi," synopsis, undated (Box 5, Folder 278)
    - "Guy Benoit," script element, undated (Box 5, Folder 279)
    - "Sadie Benning", 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 280)
    - "The Delicate Art of The Rifle," synopsis, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 281)
    - "Shirley Clarke", 1992 (Box 5, Folder 282)
    - "Committed," synopsis, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 283)
    - "Das Erste Mal (My First Time)", 1997 (Box 5, Folder 284)
    - "Detroit Rock City," synopsis, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 285)
    - "Love God, Frank Grow," synopsis, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 286)
    - "Good Grief": Burn Collector Film Zine, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 287)
    - "I, Doll", 1996 (Box 5, Folder 288)
    - "Karma Kamikaze," Sarah Kernochan, script, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 289)
    - "Kiss Me Deadly", revised script, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 290)
    - "Jeff Krulick", 1995-2001 (Box 5, Folder 291)
    - "George Kuchar": folder 1 of 3, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 292)
    - "George Kuchar": Book of Dreams, folder 2 of 3, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 293)
    - "George Kuchar:" Ideas and Notes for Essays and Screenplays, folder 3 of 3, 181 (Box 5, Folder 294)
    - "Marne Lucas, Jacob Pander", 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 295)
    - "Jesus' Son," Alison Maclean, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 296)
    - "Margarita Happy Hour," synopsis, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 297)
    - "J. Michael McCarthy", undated (Box 5, Folder 298)
    - Matt McCormick, Auto-Cinemetic Periperial Produce Instruction Manual, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 299)
    - "Matt McCormick," Rodeo Film Company, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 300)
    - "Dave Markey," Black Flag and Painted Willie, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 301)
    - "Mr Lady," Rae Carland, Kaia Wilson, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 302)
    - "Biilly Nayer Show," BNS Chronicles, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 303)
    - "Paul's TV Pitches", undated (Box 5, Folder 304)
    - "Personal Victory [Velocity]," synopsis, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 305)
    - "Raymond Pettibon," Just Happy To Be Working, 1985-1997 (Box 5, Folder 306)
    - "Pray For Rock and Roll," synopsis, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 307)
    - "Sarah Price," Caesar's Park, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 308)
    - "The Provisional M.O.," film catalogue, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 309)
    - "Jennifer Reeder," bio and filmography, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 310)
    - "Other Filmakers, Russ Forester", 1995-1998 (Box 5, Folder 311)
    - "Jack Sargeant", 1997 (Box 5, Folder 312)
    - "Kal Seeman," Artbots, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 313)
    - "Slums of Beverly Hills," synopsis, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 314)
    - "Some Nudity Required," synopsis, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 315)
    - "Andy Warhol," The Films of Andy Warhol, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 316)
    - "John Waters," Cecil B. Demented, synopsis and bio, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 317)
    - "Whatever Film," press notes, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 318)
    - "Bill Viola," A 25-year Survey,exhibit program, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 319)
    - "Danny Potnick," bio, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 320)
    - "Jon Moritsugu," Mod-Fuck Explosion, synopsis, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 321)
    - "Ruth Leithman," bio, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 322)
    - "Hard Core Logo," synopsis, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 323)
- Series VII: Printed Material
  Series VII contains magazine and newspaper clippings that Sarah Jacobson collected. Quotation marks are used to indicate Jacobsons original folder title or heading. Material is arranged chronologically.
  - Subseries A: Articles
    - "Cool Film Articles", 1980-1998 (Box 5, Folder 325)
    - "Pop Culture, Punk", 1988 (Box 5, Folder 326)
    - "Sassy," Magazine, March 1988 (Box 5, Folder 326A)
    - "Pop Culture: Men Freaking Out", 1991-1993 (Box 5, Folder 327)
    - "Pop Culture, People." Roseanne article, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 328)
    - "Pop Culture, Roseanne", 1991 (Box 5, Folder 329)
    - "Pop Culture, Roseanne", 1994-2002 (Box 5, Folder 330)
    - "Pop Culture, Serial Killers", 1991-1994 (Box 5, Folder 331)
    - "Pop Culture, Feminist Women's Stuff", 1991-2000 (Box 5, Folder 332)
    - "Pop Culture, Pop Culture Stuff", 1991-2002 (Box 5, Folder 333)
    - "Sassy," Magazine: April 1992 (Box 5, Folder 334)
    - "Pop Culture, Playboy," Magazine September 1992 (Box 5, Folder 335)
    - "Pop Culture, Shannon Doherty," clippings, 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 336)
    - "Pop Culture, L7," clippings, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 337)
    - "Pop Culture Stuff," clippings, 1992-1996 (Box 5, Folder 338)
    - "Pop Culture, Kurt, Nirvana, Grundge," clippings, 1992-1997 (Box 5, Folder 339)
    - "Movie Lists", 1993 (Box 5, Folder 340)
    - "Pop Culture, River Phoenix," People Magazine, November 1993 (Box 5, Folder 341)
    - "ETC...Misc Film Events," flyers, 1993-1999 (Box 5, Folder 342)
    - "Dirty Ben Magazine," Spring 1994 (Box 5, Folder 343)
    - "Sassy," Magazine, January 1994 (Box 5, Folder 344)
    - "Pop Culture, Shannon [Doherty]," Playboy Magazine, March 1994 (Box 5, Folder 345)
    - "Pop Culture, Courtney [Love]," clippings, 1994-1997 (Box 5, Folder 346)
    - "Pop Culture, Beat [Generation]," clippings, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 347)
    - "Pop Culture, Girl Stuff," clippings, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 348)
    - "Film Articles," clippings, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 349)
    - "Pop Culture, Roseanne", 1991 (Box 5, Folder 350)
    - "Pop Culture, S.C.A.M." Super Kick-Ass Magazine Quarterly, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 351)
    - "Spin," Magazine May 2001 (Box 5, Folder 352)
    - "Rock Films," Res Magazine, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 353)
    - "Pop Culture News Clippings", 2003 (Box 5, Folder 354)
    - "Lollipop Generation", undated (Box 5, Folder 355)
    - "Reading Lists," The Peck School Suggested Summer Reading, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 324)
  - Subseries B: Books (Box 12, Box 13)
  - Subseries C: 2018 Accretion
    Subseries C: 2018 Accretion has freelance writing from 1995-1998 for independent fanzines and underground film and music publications such as Filth and Film Threat as well as commercial publications Sassy and YM.
    - Film magazines, 2001-2004 (Box 38, Folder 14-15)
- Series VIII: Teaching Materials
  Series VIII contains Sarah Jacobson's administrative documents from courses and workshops she taught. Includes teaching notes, contracts, and flyers. Arranged chronologically.
  - Flyer, Film Arts Foundation Workshop, [1994-1995] (Box 6, Folder 356)
  - South Eastern Media Institute, information pack and contract, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 357)
  - New School University evaluation forms, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 358)
  - "Indie Calls Fall '01," New School University, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 359)
  - New School University, information pack and contract, 2001-2001 (Box 6, Folder 360)
  - "16mm Class Spring 2002, New School University (Box 6, Folder 361)
  - "Indie Class Fall '02," New School University, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 362)
  - "School Things to Copy", New School University, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 363)
  - "School Things to Copy," New School University, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 364)
  - "Film Seminar Notes," AIVF Master Class Series, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 365)
  - "Indie Class Spring '03," New School University, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 366)
  - "Sample Budget Contracts," New School University, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 367)
  - "Amy Hobby Class Notes," New School University, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 368)
- Series IX: Nostalgia, Neat Things
  Series IX: contains materials that Sarah Jacobson collected and then filed as "Nostalgia, Neat Things." Materials include, juvenillia, comics, clippings, flyers, artifacts. Arranged chronologically. See also Oversize for related material.
  - Betty and Me, No 5, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 369)
  - Jughead, No 259, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 370)
  - The Wiz, synopsis, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 370A)
  - Archie's Jokes, No 507, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 371)
  - Archie's Joke Book, No 280, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 372)
  - Betty and Veronica, No 312, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 373)
  - Modesty Blaise, #1, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 374)
  - The American New Wave: 1958-1967, The Walker Art Center, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 374A)
  - Modesty Blaise, #5, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 375)
  - "Lee's Bio," essay on Sarah Jacobson by Lee Jacobson, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 376)
  - Edina High School Class of 1989 Year Book (Box 6, Folder 377)
  - Edina High School Diploma, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 378)
  - Star Jam Comics, Featuring the Stars of Beverly Hills 090210, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 379)
  - Star Jam Comics, The Scoop on 90210, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 380)
  - Star Wars Insider, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 381)
  - Star Jam Comics, The Stars of Beverly Hills 90210, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 382)
  - Modesty Blaise, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 383)
  - "Jews of the '70s," postcards, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 384)
  - "Jews of the '70s," postcards, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 385)
  - correspondence, tattoos, clippings, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 385A)
  - "Nightmare Before Christmas," pencil, undated (Box 6, Folder 386)
  - Nightmare Before Christmas," pin, undated (Box 6, Folder 387)
  - "Nixon Again," pin, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 388)
  - Gene Simmons, Andre the Giant, stickers, undated (Box 6, Folder 389)
  - "Become the Media: Reference Guide to a Revolution," Punk Planet, clipping, undated (Box 6, Folder 390)
  - Carnival of Chaos: On the Road with the Nomadic Festival, fanzine, undated (Box 6, Folder 391)
  - Untitled independent fanzine, undated (Box 6, Folder 392)
- Series X: Miscellaneous
  Series X contains miscellaneous personal items collected by Sarah Jacobson. Includes professional directories, pamplets and course documents. Arranged chronologically.
  - Taoist Ways to Transform Stress into Vitality, workbook, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 404)
  - SIA, Survivors of Incest Anonymous, pamphlet, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 405)
  - Andy Warhol's Video and Televsion, Whitney Museum of American Art, exhibit, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 406)
  - Writer's Guild of America, Members Directory, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 407)
  - Journal, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 408)
  - Director's Guild of America, Directory of Members, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 409)
  - Planned Parenthood release form, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 410)
  - Cinema Course 344: Rock Music Films, workbook, undated (Box 6, Folder 411)
  - Al-Anon Family Inter-group, pamphlet, undated (Box 6, Folder 412)
  - New York's Guide to Great Outdoors, A Rough Guide, undated (Box 6, Folder 413)
- Series XI: Media Access Copies
  Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
  Series XI contains media accessible to researchers from the Sarah G. Jacobson Papers.
  - Subseries A: Video recording Access Copies
    - Mary Jane: DVD, 1996 (Case 157.0002)
      Original format: DVD, Access Copy
  - Subseries B: Film Access Copies
  - Subseries C: Sound recording Access Copies
    - Stains: "Fee Waybill Interview", 1999 (Case 157.0120)
      Audio cassette access copy available.
      Original format: Audio Cassette, Access Copy
      Duration: A) 30 minutes B) 8 minutes
    - Sleaze: "Maureen Interview, Sleaze", undated (Case 157.0122)
      Duration: A) 30 minutes B) 30 minutes
    - Sleaze: "Ian Mackaye, Sleaze", undated (Case 157.0124)
      Duration: A) 45 minutes B) 35 minutes
    - VH1: "Radical Cheerleaders, Mary X-mess", undated (Case 157.0126)
    - VH1: "A) Radical Cheerleaders #2 B) Aimee and Cara", undated (Case 157.0128)
      Duration: A) 30 minutes B) 10 minutes
    - VH1: "A) Samantha Radical Cheerleeders B) Mary X-mess Spin Pt 1", April 23, 2001; December 4, 2001 (Case 157.0130)
    - VH1: "George Moll, Behind the Music", undated (Case 157.0132)
      Duration: A) 25 minutes B) unknown
    - VH1: "Gay Rosenthal, Behind the Music", 1999 (Case 157.0134)
      Duration: A) 30 minutes B) 25 minutes
    - Oxygen Media: "Audra Tour Stories", 1999 (Case 157.0136)
    - Oxygen Media: "Audra, ISW", 1999 (Case 157.0138)
    - Writing File: "Kurt and Courtney", undated (Case 157.0140)
      Duration: A) 30 mintues B) 15 minutes
    - Writing File:: "A) Nick Broomfield B) Cube", undated (Case 157.0142)
      Duration: A) 45 minutes B) 20 minutes
    - Writing File: "Caroline Coon Tape 1", August 1998 (Case 157.0144)
    - Writing File: "Caroline Coon Tape 2", August 1998 (Case 157.0146)
      Duration: A) 20 minutes B) unknown
    - Writing File: "George Kuchar", undated (Case 157.0148)
    - Writing File: "Tori Interview" YM Magazine, February 27, 2002 (Case 157.0150)
    - Writing File: "Allison Anders, Things Behind the Sun #1", undated (Case 157.0152)
    - Writing File: "Allison Anders, Things Behind the Sun #2", 1992-1994 (Case 157.0154)
    - Writing File: Run Lola Run, undated (Case 157.0156)
      Duration: A) 30 minutes B) 20 minutes
    - Writing File: "Penelope Spheeris Sept. 1998" (Case 157.0158)
      Duration: A) 45 minutes B) unknown
    - Writing File: "Christina Kelly, Sassy Pt 1", undated (Case 157.0160)
    - Writing File: "Christina Kelly, Sassy Pt 2, undated (Case 157.0162)
      Duration: A) 30 minutes B) 5 minutes
    - Writing File: "A) Mary X-mess Spin, Pt 2 B) Steve Duncombe", December 4, 2001; unknown (Case 157.0164)
      Duration: A) 20 minutes B) 25 minutes
    - Writing File: "Mark Mothersbaugh!!", 1992-1994 (Case 157.0166)
    - Writing File: "Tamra YM Interview", undated (Case 157.0168)
    - Writing File: "A) Don Letts B) Katja von Gernier Pt 1", undated (Case 157.0170)
      Duration: A) 20 minutes B) 30 minutes
    - Writing File: "Katja Von Gernier Pt 2", undated (Case 157.0172)
    - Writing File: "A) Cool Teen Favita B) Nikki Reed ", June 26, 2002; June 29, 2002 (Case 157.0174)
    - Writing File: "Rosewood Follow Up Questions 2/28 and 3/1" YM Article, February 28- March 1,2002 (Case 157.0176)
    - "Babes: Lori Barbero," Babes in Toyland, February 1997 (Case 157.0178)
    - "Lori and Dale," Babes in Toyland, undated (Case 157.0180)
    - "Dale and Lori," Babes in Toyland, undated (Case 157.0182)
      Duration: A) 45 minutes B) 30 minutes.
    - "Babes: Lori," Babes in Toyland, undated (Case 157.0184)
      Duration: A) 45 minutes B) 45 minutes
    - "Babes: Dana, Kat," Babes in Toyland, undated (Case 157.0186)
      Duration: A) 25 minutes B) 25 minutes
    - "Babes: Dana," Babes in Toyland, undated (Case 157.0188)
    - "Steve Albini", August 24, 1998 (Case 157.0190)
      Duration: A) 45 minutes B) 15 minutes
    - "A) Radical Cheerleaders #1 B) Aimee and Cara", undated (Case 157.0192)
    - "Allison Anders", June 1999 (Case 157.0194)
      Original format: Audiocassette, Access Copy
    - "Becky Johnson Tape 1", undated (Case 157.0196)
    - "Becky Johnson Tape 2", 1992 (Case 157.0198)
      Duration: A) 30 minutes B) unknown
    - "Carine Alder Interview", undated (Case 157.0200)
      Duration: A) 35 minutes B) unknown
    - "Carla Rockergrrl #1", undated (Case 157.0202)
    - "Carla Rockergrrl #2", undated (Case 157.0204)
    - "Debbie Gordon Tape 1", undated (Case 157.0206)
    - "Debbie Gordon Tape 2", undated (Case 157.0208)
    - "Jenny L", undated (Case 157.0210)
    - "Joe O' Neill Tape 1", undated (Case 157.0212)
    - "Joe O' Neill Tape 2", undated (Case 157.0214)